pubrevenue.com 2014-10-01

# Pub Revenue - Innovate to Maximise Profits

## Privacy Policy

**Pub Revenue Privacy Policy**

Pub Revenue provides a Technology that places in-text advertising onto our network of publishers’ websites across the web. We also have a technology platform (the “Platform”) that helps us understand whether Users interact with our Technology and how they interact with the Technology. This Privacy Policy describes what information we gather from Users from the Site, how we use that information, and what we do to protect it. 

**The Information Pub Revenue Collects via the Technology and Platform**

Pub Revenue collects non-personally identifiable information from many of the websites in which our Technology is enabled. We use that information to deliver targeted advertising on many other websites you may visit. Pub Revenue uses cookies in connection with our Technology. Pub Revenue automatically collects certain non-personally identifiable information from your web browser in connection with our Technology and stores this information on our Platform. This information may include Internet Protocol address, web browser type, the URL of the web pages or sites you visit where our Technology is enabled, the date/time you visit those web pages or sites, and URL that of the web page you were on prior to visiting the web page where our Technology is enabled. Pub Revenue uses the information that we collect via our Technology to understand and analyze the way our Users interact with our Technology, to serve more relevant advertising, to improve the way our Technology and Platform operate, and for ad delivery and reporting purposes. 

**Data Security**

Pub Revenue uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security all information under our control. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the 100% security of any information you transmit to Pub Revenue, and you do so at your own risk. We make commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is no guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. 

**Data Protection Rights**

You may access, update, and correct, rectify or delete your personally identifiable information, and may change your marketing preferences at any time, by accessing your account online, by contacting Customer Service through the Company contact information below. Please note, however, that choosing to delete some types of personal information may prevent us from supplying certain services to you as a client. In order to better protect you and safeguard your information, we take steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections to your information. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically without further notice to you and this will be reflected by the effective date below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. 

_Effective Date: This Privacy Policy was last modified on May 2014._

_Pub Revenue Contact Information: Please contact Pub Revenue with any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice at email: mitch@pubrevenue.com._
